

CONTACT ME AT

Cell: 971 - 240 -1084 Spring Hill, TN mpadinds@gmail.com



<u>my portfolio</u>



in @michaelparker



@m-pad studios

SKILLS SUMMARY

Soft -

Empathy

Time Management

Collaboration

Curiosity

Applied -

Prototyping

Front-end

Python

programming

JavaScript 3 years exp HTML, HTML5 3 years exp

CSS Frameworks

Bootstrap

3 years exp

3 years exp

Tools -

Figma

Adobe XD

Visual Studio Code GitHub

3 years exp

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION-CS CLASSES TAKEN AT WOU

Algorithms

Data Structures

Web development

Python

JavaScript

Computer Organization

Discrete Math

Intro to Computer Science AWARDS RECEIVED



Honor roll (2008 - 2010)

MICHAEL PARKER

ASPIRING UX DESIGNER

PERSONAL PROFILE

College graduate with over 6+ years of experience as produce department management and 4+ years in outpatient physical therapy clinics. Wanting to pivot careers utilizing my experiences and skills into the software development industry as a Junior UX designer.

PROJECTS

Blondy's Baked Goods

Lead UX designer

- Designed in Figma for the wireframes and prototypes.
- Prototype showcases the functionality of the app.
- A mobile, desktop, and tablet E-Commerce web app designed for a local baker to allow her goods to be more accessible to the community.

The Omni Logger

Lead UX designer and coder

- Built using Django, Bootstrap, JS Charts, and SQLite.
- A mobile and desktop app designed to help users track everyday life activities. These activities include journal entries, workouts, and much more. The data is then used to build beautiful charts.

My Portfolio

Lead UX designer and coder

- Built using Vue.js, Node.js, and Bootstrap 5.
- Case study wireframes, mockups, and prototypes built in Figma.
- A portfolio showcasing my projects, skill set, and who I am.

CERTIFICATE

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

by Google

A 7-course, 28 week-long certification that involved learning industry-related UX design. Everything I learned included:

- entry-level UX designer's job duties
- design sprints
 - - visual design
 - user research
 - wireframing and prototyping
 - Adobe XD, Figma, and how to make my own portfolio site.
 - Empathy maps, user stories, and personas
- UX design frameworks: LeanUX, Double Diamond, and Design Thinking.

MICHAEL PARKER

ASPIRING UX DESIGNER

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Western Oregon University

Bachelors of Science | Majored in Exercise Science & Minored in Linguistics | Sept 2010 - June 2015

Chemeketa Community College

Transfer degree in Health to WOU | Sept 2008 - 2010

WORK EXPERIENCE

Produce Manager

Natural Grocers | Jan 2016 - present

- Track monthly COGs using produce maintenance software.
- Train new staff on produce company policies and procedures.
- Building rapport with vendors while driving sales for the department.
- Create an engaging, welcoming customer experience by making the department accessible to shop while aesthetically pleasing.
- Maintain clean, fresh, and organized produce department for better customer experience.

Assistant Produce Manager

Natural Grocers | Sept 2015 - Jan 2016

• Order for department, setup wet rack and dry rack, help in inventory, cashier, help train general staff assigned to department, receive and break down orders.

Physical Therapy Tech

BenchMark PT | Jan 2011 - Sept 2015

- Assist physical therapists with their patient's plan of care.
- Build rapport with patients by empathizing with them, being professional at all times, and putting their plan of care as top priority.
- Run patients through their exercise regiment or treat with ultra sound and/or E-Stim setups with heat or ice.